Ronny Haase

✓ ronhaase@gmail.com
✓ ronnyhaase.com
✓ @ronnyhaase
✓ /ronnyhaase

♥ Liverpooler Strasse 213349 BerlinGermany

🛘 +49 (0)151 10 59 37 40 🕒 r n y h s e

Hi! I'm Ronny, 29 years old and currently based in Berlin.

I'm developing web based solutions for over 10 years with focus on Frontend Development for ~4 years.

Beside excellent knowledge in JavaScript, HTML 5 and CSS 3, as well as testing, optimizing, and debugging for Browsers and JavaScript Engines, I love deliberating about good Design, coding in NodeJS, and thinking about scalable Web applications and services.

Key Skills



Work Experience

07/2013 – present Freelancer Germany

Frontend Developer // Web Application Developer & -Architekt

- JavaScript-Development for mobile hybrid app ",Xanten-App" (see Sample works)
- Design & Implementation of a responsive solution for weeze.de

07/2013 - 09/2013 Parental leave

07/2012 - 06/2013	the a-team GmbH	Berlin, Germany
	Frontend Developer	
•	 Lead Frontend Development for flagship product "iCMP", it's modernization and redevelopment including a in-house JavaScript framework Frontend Development of websites, software solutions and iCMP modules. Development of jQuery Plugins 	
•		
•		
09/2011 - 06/2012	Freelancer	Germany
	Frontend Developer // Web Application Developer & -Architect • Among others, Frontend Development of "PPM" for Dirk Rossmann GmbH (see Sample	
•		
	works)	
08/2004 - 08/2011	Freelancer (as a side job)	Berlin, Germany
	Web Developer & -Designer	
01/2004 - 06/2004	BBJ Servis gGmbH	Berlin, Germany
	Software- & Database-Develope	r
09/2000 - 08/2003	Devcon Software GmbH	Berlin, Germany
	Trainee as "IT Specialist, Applicat	ion Development"
Publications		
11/2011	1 "PopcornJS – Das HTML5-Media-Framework" Webstandards magazine issue 12/2011 - 2 pages	
Education		
10.2009 - 09.2011	Humboldt University of Berlin	Berlin, Germany
	Study of Computer Science	
08.2004 - 06.2008	Treptow-Kolleg	Berlin, Germany
	A-Level / Abitur	
09.2000 - 08.2003	Devcon Software GmbH	Berlin, Germany
	Trainee as "IT Specialist, Application Development"	
Others		
09/2008 - 05/2009	Civilian service at Helene-Häusler-Schule, special school	

Interests & Skills

Languages German Native language

Englisch Fluent

Hobbies & Interests Music, Design, Technology, Photography, Social Media

Berlin, 13.10.2013